<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://seunbite.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://seunbite.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2026-01-05T04:18:24+00:00</updated><id>https://seunbite.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">What I like</title><link href="https://seunbite.github.io/blog/2026/WhatIlike/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What I like"/><published>2026-01-04T10:40:16+00:00</published><updated>2026-01-04T10:40:16+00:00</updated><id>https://seunbite.github.io/blog/2026/WhatIlike</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://seunbite.github.io/blog/2026/WhatIlike/"><![CDATA[<p>Like</p> <ul> <li>Cutlery (Yes, spoon)</li> <li>Banana (I think their appearance makes me happy)</li> <li>Woody scent (Do you know that koreans have a deep preference to the woody fregrance bacause of their forests?)</li> <li>Post-traumatic Growth</li> <li>Cute robots</li> <li>People with non-human friends</li> <li>Classic watch</li> <li>Stars</li> <li>Flan</li> <li>K-food (This is a given. I can talk about this for 5 days)</li> <li>Axolotl (The cutest)</li> <li>Movie with a nice plot (I like the pose-traumatic growth. Share me your favorite!)</li> <li>Personality Talk (I studied psychology but I like to talk about MBTI the shit. Sorry. I really like the environment to freely talk about themselves and their personality. I also like the story of getting-to-know of both extremes.)</li> <li>Evolutionary psychology (lowkey)</li> </ul> <p>Dislike coming soon</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="me"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like Cutlery (Yes, spoon) Banana (I think their appearance makes me happy) Woody scent (Do you know that koreans have a deep preference to the woody fregrance bacause of their forests?) Post-traumatic Growth Cute robots People with non-human friends Classic watch Stars Flan K-food (This is a given. I can talk about this for 5 days) Axolotl (The cutest) Movie with a nice plot (I like the pose-traumatic growth. Share me your favorite!) Personality Talk (I studied psychology but I like to talk about MBTI the shit. Sorry. I really like the environment to freely talk about themselves and their personality. I also like the story of getting-to-know of both extremes.) Evolutionary psychology (lowkey)]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why I transitioned from psychology to CS</title><link href="https://seunbite.github.io/blog/2025/WhyAI/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why I transitioned from psychology to CS"/><published>2025-11-24T15:40:16+00:00</published><updated>2025-11-24T15:40:16+00:00</updated><id>https://seunbite.github.io/blog/2025/WhyAI</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://seunbite.github.io/blog/2025/WhyAI/"><![CDATA[<p>I love psychology because psychologists come up with the very clever ideas how to measure the unseen human mind (operational definitions).</p> <ul> <li>Agressiveness by giving hot sauce (<a href="https://www.semanticscholar.org/paper/A-hot-new-way-to-measure-aggression%3A-Hot-sauce-Lieberman-Solomon/3a789895c3e18f9e3356e98feda68521b726f294">Lieberman, 1999</a>)</li> <li>Conscientiousness by Room cleanness (<a href="https://www.apa.org/pubs/journals/releases/psp-823379.pdf">Gosling, 2002</a>)</li> </ul> <p>However, I found myself wanting a more direct and faster way to test and demonstrate my hypotheses about the social desire and fulfillment of humans. I am truely interested in dealing robot as new social cue stimuli based on strong assumption that human has weak and attackable censoring system to the social sign from other one. I like the numeric tables and plots which can intuitively and reproductively show the contribution of the study.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="me"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[FAQ that I love to answer]]></summary></entry></feed>